{
    "subject": "resource/Bernard_Mary_of_Jesus",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:Italian_beatified_people",
    "human_readable": "Bernard Mary of Jesus is a subject related to Category:Italian beatified people.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9393197298049927,
            "question": "Is Bernard Mary of Jesus Italian?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8878697752952576,
            "question": "What category does Bernard Mary of Jesus belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7126291990280151,
            "question": "Who is Bernard Mary of Jesus?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.712046205997467,
            "question": "How does Bernard Mary of Jesus contribute to our understanding of Italian religious history?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6879972219467163,
            "question": "Can you name other notable figures in the category of 'Italian beatified people'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6642895936965942,
            "question": "What are some common characteristics shared by individuals in the category of 'Italian beatified people'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.566166877746582,
            "question": "Are there any specific events or contributions associated with Bernard Mary of Jesus?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5195555686950684,
            "question": "What is the significance of being a 'beatified person' in Italian culture and history?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.32745838165283203,
            "question": "What are some resources for learning more about Bernard Mary of Jesus?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2647188603878021,
            "question": "What does it mean for someone to be 'beatified'?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Bernard Mary of Jesus is a subject related to Category:Italian beatified people.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2284_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some resources for learning more about Bernard Mary of Jesus?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2284_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the significance of being a 'beatified person' in Italian culture and history?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2284_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any specific events or contributions associated with Bernard Mary of Jesus?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2284_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2284_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2284_126.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2284_139.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2284_168.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2284_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2284_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2284_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2284_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2284_82.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2284_93.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the provided context information, I have determined that:\n\n* The document file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_2284/re-ranker-msmarco/81.txt does not mention Category:Italian beatified people.\n* The document file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_2284/re-ranker-msmarco/33.txt does mention that Blessed Bernard Mary of Jesus is a \"beatified\" person, but it does not specify the category.\n* The document file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_2284/re-ranker-msmarco/123.txt and file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_2284/re-ranker-msmarco/61.txt do mention Category:Italian beatified people is not mentioned but mentions Saint bernard which is a different person.\n\nTherefore, the information in the documents does NOT support the triple that Bernard Mary of Jesus is a subject related to Category:Italian beatified people. \n\nHere is the response in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Blessed Bernard Mary of Jesus, including his birthplace (Rome), the year of his birth (1831), and that he was a member of the Passionist order. Additionally, it mentions his beatification by Pope John Paul II in 1988. Given this context, it is reasonable to infer that Bernard Mary of Jesus is indeed a subject related to \"Category:Italian beatified people,\" as beatification typically involves individuals recognized within Catholicism for their piety and holiness, many of whom are Italian due to the historical prominence of Italy in the Catholic Church's center."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "Caesar Silvestrelli is the birth name of Bernard Mary of Jesus, but he was not born in Italy.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}